module.exports = [
    {
        greeting: "Welcome to the Map Game. Your question:",
        question: "What is the westernmost point to the lower 48 states?",
        answer: "Cape Alava, WA",
        center: {lat: 39.8282, lng: -98.5795},
        position: {lat: 48.1647572, lng: -124.7331501},
        questionZoom: 4,
        answerZoom: 9,
        visible: false,
        // styles: mapStyle
    },
    {
        greeting: "Congratulations! You found the marker. We have instantly moved you to the next question.",
        question: "This city on America’s largest river shares a name with the capital of Egypt.",
        answer: "Cairo, IL",
        center: {lat: 39.8282, lng: -98.5795},
        position: {lat: 37.0058053, lng: -89.1777963},
        answerZoom: 9,
        visible: false,
        // styles: mapStyle
    },
    {
        greeting: "Congratulations! You found the marker. We have instantly moved you to the next question.",
        question: "This island is a volcanic cone in America’s deepest Lake. Wizard Island.",
        answer: "Crater Lake, OR",
        center: {lat: 39.8282, lng: -98.5795},
        position: {lat: 42.938841, lng: -122.145989},
        answerZoom: 9,
        visible: false,
        // styles: mapStyle
    },
    {
        greeting: "Congratulations! You found the marker. We have instantly moved you to the next question.",
        question: "Where is the site of largest active alpine glacier in the lower 48 states?",
        answer: "Mt Rainer, WA",
        center: {lat: 39.8282, lng: -98.5795},
        position: {lat: 46.852148, lng: -121.757732},
        answerZoom: 9,
        visible: false,

        // styles: mapStyle
    },
    {
        greeting: "Congratulations! You found the marker. We have instantly moved you to the next question.",
        question: "This is the tallest mountain east of the Mississippi River.",
        answer: "Mt Mitchell, NC",
        center: {lat: 39.8282, lng: -98.5795},
        position: {lat: 35.764963, lng: -82.265140},
        answerZoom: 9,
        visible: false,
        // styles: mapStyle
    },
    {
        greeting: "Congratulations! You found the marker. We have instantly moved you to the next question.",
        question: "This is the location of America’s largest caldera.",
        answer: "Yellowstone, WY",
        center: {lat: 39.8282, lng: -98.5795},
        position: {lat: 44.427801, lng: -110.588431},
        answerZoom: 9,
        visible: false,
        // styles: mapStyle
    },
    {
        greeting: "Congratulations! You found the marker. We have instantly moved you to the next question.",
        question: "This site in America is known as “the Four Corners”.",
        answer: "Border of CO, AZ, UT, and NM",
        center: {lat: 39.8282, lng: -98.5795},
        position: {lat: 36.999082, lng: -109.045224},
        answerZoom: 9,
        visible: false,
        // styles: mapStyle
    },
    {
        greeting: "Congratulations! You found the marker. We have instantly moved you to the next question.",
        question: "This largest city in FL lies on one of the few rivers that flows from South to North.",
        answer: "Jacksonville, FL",
        center: {lat: 39.8282, lng: -98.5795},
        position: {lat: 30.324650, lng: -81.659913},
        answerZoom: 9,
        visible: false,
        // styles: mapStyle
    },
    {
        greeting: "Congratulations! You found the marker. We have instantly moved you to the next question.",
        question: "What is the largest city on the shore of the smallest Great Lake?",
        answer: "Toronto, ON",
        center: {lat: 39.8282, lng: -98.5795},
        position: {lat: 43.645147, lng: -79.380863},
        answerZoom: 9,
        visible: false,
        // styles: mapStyle
    },
    {
        greeting: "Congratulations! You found the marker. We have instantly moved you to the next question.",
        question: "The city got its current name from railroad engineer J. Edgar Thompson. It’s thought to be a shortened version of “Atlantica-Pacifica.”",
        answer: "Atlanta, GA",
        center: {lat: 39.8282, lng: -98.5795},
        position: {lat: 33.748777, lng: -84.388246},
        answerZoom: 9,
        visible: false,
        // styles: mapStyle
    },
    
];
